This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
Munkini and Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, impelled down.
With the assistance of Ivankov, the Queen of Newcomerland,
Luffy was finally able to make it to level six,
only to discover that Ace was already gone.
I assure you, resistance is futile.
Luffy!
Your brother's a pirate.
His fate was sealed the moment he stepped in this prison.
Dammit, Luffy.
I'd hoped Hancock was lying.
It was a simple plan, but it defeated us nonetheless.
As much as I hate to admit it, we're trapped here on level six,
at least for the time being.
As far as Ace Boy in the Navy goes,
that ship has already sailed, literally.
Give up on him, okay?
Or rather, put your faith in Whitebeard.
There's no way he'd give up on one of his own.
He'll come up with something.
I'm leaving.
Huh?
I'm going to Marineford.
Look, if I give up now,
I'll regret it.
You can do as you like,
but first of all,
how do you propose we get off this floor?
If you want out that bad,
then set me free.
I'll make a hole in the ceiling
and you'll be free to go.
Sound good?
Crocodile!
Just like old times, huh?
Did you miss me?
The ultimate team is formed!
Shaking Impel down!
You know, for the life of me,
I couldn't think of a good reason to break out of here.
But Whitebeard and the Navy are going to start a war?
This is my chance to bring down that old man once and for all.
This clash of powers has piqued my interest.
And I've just the tools at my disposal
to get us a front row seat to the action.
You scratch my back and I'll scratch yours.
Not a bad proposition, is it?
Screw that crap!
You messed up Phoebe's whole country, you jerk!
You can rock down here!
That was a long time ago.
That place is no longer of any interest to me.
However you may feel, we still need his help.
If we have an opportunity to escape from here,
then we're obliged to take it.
What?
Are you crazy, Eva?
Do you know what this guy...
There's no time to be hoity-toity.
Sandy Pants here is our only ticket outside.
Hello, Ifankov.
My, my, it's been a long time.
Eh, Crocoboy?
Hey, wait, you two know each other?
Just a passing acquaintance.
I met him when he was a rookie, all wet behind the ears.
I wouldn't worry.
If this guy tries to double-cross us,
I'll whip him into shape in a jiffy.
As long as I've got an eye on him,
then he should behave just fine.
He is a scoundrel,
but he's a scoundrel with a weakness I know well.
Hey, if you so much as mention a word of that, I'll...
Easy there.
Sure you want to take that snippy tone with me, Crocoboy?
Because I'd be more than happy
to reveal your sordid past right now.
Grr.
Or you can shut that mouth of yours,
help us out,
and keep your dirty little secret.
Hee-haw!
Grr.
Cocky bastard.
Hey, you guys, while you're at it,
you should let me out of here, too.
Me, too, me, too!
I got a boat to pick with Whitebeard!
Yeah, let me out, too!
Aw!
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh!
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh!
Shut up!
Deaf-wing!
Please, have mercy on me.
I beg you to take me with you.
I will be of great service.
I've known your brother Ace
since he first joined the Whitebeard Pirates.
He's a good friend.
And I know you too, from all the stories he's told.
I'm not like the others down here.
I was arrested because I objected to his execution.
I want to help save Ace too.
I swear, I will put my life on the line for him.
Hmm.
Jinbei, the first son of the sea.
If they imprisoned him here,
then he must have relinquished his title
as one of the Seven Warlords.
That would mean his self-proclaimed bond with Ace
has merit indeed.
All right, then.
Wait, are you sure?
You've never even met this man,
and he's most assuredly dangerous.
It'll be fine.
Just let him out, okay?
You have my gratitude.
Me next!
I like Ace too!
I'll die for him and stuff!
You boys are asking for a death!
Two Warlords, or two former Warlords, that is.
Wait a sec.
This guy?
For real?
You won't regret this.
I will fight to protect Ace,
even if it means my own end.
If you think you can stop the war
between the Navy and Whitebeard,
go ahead and try.
I don't give a damn either way.
As long as I get a shot at that crusty old bastard,
it's worth it for me.
If you think I'll let you lay a single finger
on Whitebeard, you're wrong.
Well, then, why don't you just try and stop me?
Crocco Boy, your secret past,
remember?
It's settled, then.
Let's get moving.
We don't have much time.
With a team this formidable,
not even Impel Down can hold us.
Yee-haw!
All units, load up.
Move out.
Use your prison bullets.
Prepare to deal with devil-proof powers.
We've reached level six, sir.
Move in!
What the heck?
Is that the ceiling?
Worry about that later.
Spread out and search the floor.
Do you really think they stuck around here
after making that gigantic hole,
you morons?
Shiryu!
The jail manager!
Pathetic.
It's as plain as day.
You can't do anything right without me.
What a bunch of sorry excuses for jailers.
Let me give you a hint,
so maybe you can clean up this disgrace.
While you were picking your noses,
the three prisoners you're looking for
released Crocodile and Jinbei.
And then climbed up through that hole
to level five.
I want you to pass along a message for me.
Tell Magellan I'll help him if he wants.
No, that's, uh...
What?
What did you say?
They've escaped with Jinbei and Crocodile?
Yes, sir.
They're not in their cells.
No!
Are you saying that even after my brilliant plan,
they somehow weren't their way out of level six?
And then now they're a group of five roaming wild
and not sleeping like they're supposed to be?
Yes, sir.
That's correct.
Do you think I might be held responsible
for any of this nonsense?
One, Magellan is currently transporting
Portkis DAs to the Navy,
so I'm afraid you'd be responsible for all of it.
I knew you were gonna say that!
All right.
I'm gonna get out there and fight, too.
All jailers report to level four immediately.
Mistress Sadie, Salda.
Gather your forces
and head to level four this instant.
I'll be warden even if I have to risk my life.
Wait, what am I saying?
Stop those criminals
even if you have to risk your lives!
You ready to boogie, Bon Boy?
Yes!
Yes, I am, Eva!
Are you sure?
Emporio Energy Hormones
only give you strength for one day.
There will be side effects.
I know.
Go ahead and do it.
I mean, what choice do I have?
If I don't,
I won't even be able to get off the floor.
Yes, good point.
Unless I wanted to carry you.
Which, for the record,
I do not.
Emporio Energy Hormone!
Yikes, right at the jimmies.
Oopsie.
Newcomer power!
Bon, please don't die!
Is everybody ready?
Just so you know,
even if we do make it to the top of the prison,
we'll still be in for one hell of a fight.
We're completely surrounded by the Calm Belt,
which is impassable in any normal ship.
We'll have to steal a Navy vessel
if we want to go anywhere near their headquarters.
That means we need more people to join our team.
I know what you're thinking.
We have lots already.
But to be honest,
some of you won't make it out alive.
By the time we reach the top floor,
many of you won't be there to see it.
If you're captured,
you'll be tortured to death.
There will be no mercy.
So if we want to survive,
we need to set free as many prisoners as possible
while we make our way from here to Level 1.
Whether we like them or not,
we'll need their help.
If we can cause enough chaos to start a riot,
it'll help keep those jailers occupied.
That means our first step on each floor
is to open the cells
and let our new friends clear the way for us.
So let's give these boys hell!
Newcomerland is going to rattle this big cage
the likes of which they've never seen before!
Hee-haw!
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Are you ready to rock this straw hat, Roy?
He went on ahead of us.
A free spirit.
Hee-haw!
Let's catch up to him, Candy!
Hey, somebody please stop me!
I'm going too fast!
It's never been so fast before!
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
The hormone seems to be working a bit over time.
Indeed.
But check out those amazing moves.
Very nice.
It's not nice!
I'm getting sick!
Oh.
It's sick!
Yikes!
We'll be right back.
At least the Navy will remain blissfully ignorant of this disaster.
All right, back to your posts and clean up the mess inside.
Yes, sir!
It's just before ten in the morning.
The execution is at three in the afternoon.
We can be certain that they'll do everything in their power to stay on time.
So if Whitebeard is going to make an attack, it's most likely that he'll do it as soon as possible.
Ace should already be on the ship and in route.
The war could break out at any second.
But they won't kill him until three o'clock, right?
That means we still have a chance to get there and save him!
Is this supposed to slow me down?
I'll use my right hand and turn this into sand.
Let's go over how Crocodile's sand-sand devil-proof power works.
He can turn into sand as well as control it.
His right hand can suck out any type of moisture.
People and plants will wither away, while rocks and earth will turn into sand.
They're here!
Level four reporting in.
Jinbei, the warlord who escaped from level six has been sighted.
Seems we've reached the burning heat hell.
Alongside the intruder monkey, D-Luffy.
Man, it's hot.
The former warlord Crocodile is here as well.
We're prepared to engage the enemy.
Fire!
Clear the prison bullets!
Here we go!
Fishman Karate!
Huh? What just happened?
What the hell is this?
Feel my arabesque brick fish!
Straw hat! Two warlords?
What are we supposed to do?
We don't stand a chance!
Don't give up! We outnumber them at least!
We need to hold out until the reinforcements arrive!
Move it! We're in a rush!
Should be fun!
Don't you stand there! Shoot them!
Talk to me!
Vice Warden! This is level four!
You got him!
About that!
Please, come help us, sir!
Come on, boys!
Come on!
Camisole!
Long John's Teabag!
Pantyhole!
Reef!
Leggings!
Bra!
Blooms!
Reef!
All this waiting around sucks!
It's not funny anymore!
Damn!
Why are they hanging out right here?
Stupid underwear fetishists!
Just cleaning their butts must be nice!
We finally make it to level two and this is what stops us!
If the guards come, it's all for nothing!
Also, these things won't stop farting!
It's awful!
Ain't that the truth?
That was you!
I'm sorry!
Ah!
Smells like bird hair!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Oh, oh!
Oh!
Ugh!
I know!
Hm.
Holy crap!
The keys!
Now we can get out!
Thanks, buddy!
You don't know how!
Oh!
It's...
...your crocodile!
I'm thinking about breaking out of here.
But I might need a bit of assistance.
And you, you're a man of action, aren't you, Mr. One?
Now that you mention it, things are a bit boring here.
I think I might take you up on that offer, old friend.
Ophi and his companions battle their way up to level four.
Meanwhile, the prisoners on level two cause a massive riot, plunging the prison into utter chaos.
Suddenly, another infamous pirate breaks into Impel Down.
But what could be his mission?
On the next One Piece, even more chaos.
Blackbeard, teach in Vaze.
I can be king of the pirates!